A Guide to the Paul A. Weiss papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA124
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Audio-visual Material, 1940-1970; 13; 1.76 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  - Projection Slides (Box 114)
  - Microscope Slides (Box 115)
  - Microscope Slides (Box 116)
  - Microscope Slides (Box 117)
  - 2 audio recordings: Living Forms (Box 117)
    RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
  - 1966 Holiday Science Series Lectures 1-4 (also labeled as 1960) (Box 117)
- Memorabilia, 1939-1980; 14; 3 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes medals, plaques, videotape, diplomas, posters, and photographs.
  Arranged by type of material.
  - 2 plaques and 1 paperweights (Box 118)
  - Various Medals (Box 119)
  - memorabilia: Sash (Box 120)
  - "A Cell is not an Island" picture (Box 120)
  - Videotape-Medal of Science 1979 Award Ceremony January 14, 1980 at the White House, 1979 1980 (Box 120)
    RAC is unable to provide access to the original item. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
  - National Medal of Science Plaque (Box 120)
  - Signed Birthday greetings card, 1978 (Box 120)
  - US Science Exhibit, Seattle World's Fair 1962 Impressions (Box 120)
  - 2 presentation boards (Box 120)
  - Growth Society 1939 posters and pictures (Box 120)
  - Weiss lecture advertisement posters (Box 120)
  - various medals (Box 120)
  - Various plagues (Box 120)
  - Diplomas, 1940-1970s (Box 121)
  - Diplomas (Folder 1)
  - Sabre (Box 123)
- Photographs, 1925-1980; 15
  Many not identified. Representative copies made of photographs. To see all photographs in collection, ask to view original file. Two photo albums were removed.
  Includes personal photographs of Weiss' and wife's family, friends and colleagues. Also includes professional photographs of laboratories, colleagues, lectures, society and governmental meetings.
  Arranged by subject.
  - Austrian Views (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Boats (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Colleagues (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Group Photographs (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Leopold and Lilian (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - National Medal of Science, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Neuroscience Research Program, 1960-1970s (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Nina and Family (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Paul and Nina (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Schmitts (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Schloss-Steinberb (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Snapshots, 1927-1975 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Texas Apartment (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Tihany, 1929 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Valley Ranch (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Villa Rasthast, Austria (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Weiss Family (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Weiss Laboratory at RU (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Weiss Portraits (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - WWI (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - WWII (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - Photographs (Box 125)
  - Oversized photographs (albums) (Box 126)
- Lantern Slides, 16
  - Lantern Slides (Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10)
  - Lantern Slides (Box 12, Box 14, Box 15, Box D)
  - Lantern Slides (Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40)
  - Lantern Slides (Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 45)
  - Slides (Box 6830)
- Packages and Miscellaneous, 17
  - Index Cards (Box 6829)
  - Package 1
  - Package 2
  - Package 3
  - Package 4
  - Package 5
  - Package 6
  - Package 7
  - Package 8
  - Package 9